techgrapple.com 2015-04-28

# Privacy Policy & Security - Tech GrappleTech Grapple

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including [your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views, website navigation and]

(b) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters

(c) any other information that you choose to send to us; and

(d) other information.

**Cookies**

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We [may] use [both] [“session” cookies] [and “persistent” cookies] on the website. [We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website.] [We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; and]

[Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser.] [Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.]

[We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.]

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites [including this one].

You location, age, search term, sex etc., can also be used to so you relevant ads what you serve on our blog.

**Third Party Advertisement**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Using Your Personal Information**

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

(a) administer the website;

(b) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;

(c) enable your use of the services available on the website;

(d) send you general/blog/new updates (non-marketing) communications;

(e) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

(f) send to you [our newsletter and other] communications relating to our blog and financial services which we think may be of interest to you, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require those communications)

(g) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

(h) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website; and

(l) other uses.

**Disclosures**

We may disclose information about you to [any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors] insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose your personal information:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);

(d) to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

**International Data Transfers**

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

Information which you provide may be transferred to countries [(including [the United States], [Japan], [Australia], [China], [India] and [Brazil] which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area.

[In addition, [personal information that you submit for publication on the website] will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others.]

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

**Policy Amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

**Third Party Websites**

The website may contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

**Updating Information**

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

**Copyright**

We work hard to serve the users with the latest and true information. All the contents used on our site is unique and has not been copied from anywhere, coping the content from here and posting on other site (without providing source link) can be accused. Pictures added long with the article may or may not have copyright, and we try our best not to publish those images that somebody hold the copyright on. If any of the content match little bit with your content that might be coincidence, and if you come across any of the picture that is owned by you or article that you think has been copied. Please visit our contact us page and let us know.

We hold the right to approve or disapprove any comments and can also do little modification to make the comment proper for out blog. Any abusive comment and the comment with no name or user ID will not be approved.
